freepostsite.com 2011-11-07

# Privacy Policy | Free Post Site dot com

|    

#### Latest Free Posts - Show Full View

| 

> ### Privacy Policy
> 
> Free Post Site has established this privacy policy to explain to you how your information is protected, collected and used, which may be updated by Free Post Site from time to time. Free Post Site will provide notice of materially significant changes to this privacy policy by posting notice on the Free Post Site site.
> 
> #### 1\. Protecting your privacy
> 
>   * We don't run banner ads, pop ups, pop unders, or any other kind of commercial ads. 
>   * We don't share your information with third parties for marketing purposes. 
>   * We don't engage in cross-marketing or link-referral programs with other sites. 
>   * We don't employ tracking devices for marketing purposes ("cookies", "web beacons," single-pixel gifs). 
>   * We don't send you unsolicited communications for marketing purposes. 
>   * We offer email anonymization & relay, to reduce 3rd party harvesting & spam. 
>   * Account information is password-protected. Keep your password safe. 
>   * Forums use basic webserver authentication. Close your browser to log out. 
>   * Free Post Site does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If Free Post Site learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 13, Free Post Site will remove that post. 
>   * Free Post Site, or people who post on Free Post Site, may provide links to third party websites, which may have different privacy practices. We are not responsible for, nor have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited. 
> 

> 
> #### 2\. Data we collect
> 
>   * We sometimes collect your email address, for purposes such as sending self-publishing and confirmation emails, authenticating user accounts, providing subscription email services, registering for forums, etc. 
>   * For paid job postings, we collect contact information, such as name(s), phone/fax number(s), and address for billing purposes. 
>   * We sometimes collect your phone number for account authentication purposes, and may transmit it to a third party service for tele-robotic verification. 
>   * Free Post Site does not store credit card information. Credit card transactions are transmitted to a financial gateway, and we endeavor to protect the security of your payment information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. 
>   * We may collect personal information if you provide it in feedback or comments, post it on our classifieds or interactive forums, or if you contact us directly. Please do not post any personal information on Free Post Site's forums or classifieds that you expect to keep private. 
>   * Our web logs collect standard web log entries for each page served, including your IP address, page URL, and timestamp. Web logs help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Free Post Site site, and to otherwise provide our service to you. 
> 

> 
> #### 3\. Data we store
> 
>   * All classified and forum postings are stored in our database, even after "deletion," and may be archived elsewhere. 
>   * Our web logs and other records are stored indefinitely. 
>   * Registered job posters can access and update their account information through the account homepage. 
>   * Although we make good faith efforts to store the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security. 
> 

> 
> #### 4\. Archiving and display of Free Post Site postings by search engines and other sites
> 
> Search engines and other sites not affiliated with Free Post Site - including [archive.org](http://archive.org/), [](http://www.google.com/)google.com, and [](http://groups.yahoo.com/)groups.yahoo.com - archive or otherwise make available Free Post Site postings, including resumes
> 
> #### 5\. Circumstances in which Free Post Site may release information
> 
>   * Free Post Site may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. 
>   * Free Post Site may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Use; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Free Post Site, its users or the general public. 
> 

> 
> #### 6\. International Users
> 
> By visiting our web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of Free Post Site we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, please understand that such data may be stored on servers located in the United States. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.
> 
> #### 7\. Feedback
> 
> We welcome your feedback on this document in our feedback form.  
  
---|---
